Chapter 894 The Battle of Germain (1)  

   "Don't panic, Lord Seclian is here!"  

   "With Lord Seclian here, we are not afraid of any enemy!"...  

   At the same time, there were also noisy discussions on the deck. These legion reserve soldiers from various towns in the Sicilian territory of Theonia certainly knew the reputation of Seclian, but they were far from being treated like the crewmen of Theonia. respect.  

   A man wearing leather armor and a leather helmet quickly walked out of the deck. He approached the side of the ship and solemnly performed a military salute: "Sir, I am the captain of this warship, Ilias of the First Fleet!"  

   Hearing that it was his old subordinate, Seclian was relieved, and he immediately said: "I know you, Ilyas, every time the fleet's warship training and assessment is conducted, the results of the fast 3-layer oar warship you command are always Ranking at the top...Now I order you to immediately ask all the soldiers on the ship to jump into the sea for me, and then take your warship and follow me to meet the enemy!"  

   Ilias was taken aback and said hesitantly: "...but...Commander Miltias raised the Apollo flag and asked us to..."  

   "Miltias is a fool!" Seclian interrupted him angrily and shouted: "The enemies have come to kill them, and all the warships are still full of soldiers. They have no ability to fight. What's the use of gathering together? ! Is it convenient for you to be hit and sunk by the enemy! As the naval commander of the First Fleet, I now order you to execute the order immediately! "  

   "Yes...yes!" Ilias responded loudly. From the bottom of his heart, he absolutely agreed with Seclian's approach, because the belief developed by the First Fleet under the influence of Seclian was always to attack, never Being beaten passively.  

   Only the soldiers on the deck who heard the conversation between the two began to make noises. They did not want to be kicked off the ship.  

   Ilias had to face them and persuaded loudly: "Theonian warriors, our fleet is now encountering a strong enemy and the situation is urgent! But because you are loaded on the warship, the warship cannot fight. Either you Jump into the sea so that we can fight, repel the enemy, and then come back to rescue you; or you can stay on the ship, wait for the enemy ship to arrive, sink the warship, and then everyone will become prisoners together... Please make your choice now!"  

   The deck suddenly became silent, and soon a man stepped forward.  

   "Squad leader!" the soldiers shouted earnestly, focusing their hopeful eyes on him.  

   "Brothers, if the navy is destroyed, we will be in big trouble!" The squad leader said with determination: "Take your long shields and let's jump into the sea to show the navy that they are not the only ones who can swim."  

   After he finished speaking, no soldier expressed any objection, and one by one they picked up the long shields on the deck. This is the strict discipline of the Theonian Legion, even if this is just a legion reserve unit.  

   "Please help us save other armor and weapons first." The squad leader told Ilias, then he picked up his long shield and with a "plop", the first one jumped into the sea, followed by the other soldiers... ...  

   During this process, Elias kept performing military salutes.  

   After Seclian gave the order, he did not stop next to the warship, but continued to chase other warships. Since the warships were full of soldiers and were slow, it was not difficult to catch up with them. After stopping several warships one after another, , he discovered a situation: all he encountered were warships of the First Fleet (that is, warships that broke into the port of Selinus during the storm and escaped disaster), and there were many soldiers on board the warships. He is a legionary reserve soldier of Theonia.  

   Seklian thought about it for a moment and realized that this was certainly not an accident.  

   In order to seize the time, Miltias ordered at the port that the warships should be loaded with soldiers before setting off. The legion reserve soldiers were more well-trained and more organized and disciplined than the citizen soldiers of other city-states, so they could move as quickly as possible. The speed gathered at the dock and boarded the warship.  

   At the same time, Miltias was the last one to set off because he had to supervise the entire boarding process. Any military commander generally has a habit of gathering his most trusted troops around him, so that during the battle The command is more convenient and can play a greater role, although this is just a troop transport. Miltias still habitually let the warships of the First Fleet dock at the dock first, so the warships of the Fourth Fleet, which had been with him for more than ten years, set off later and were closer to him.  

   Miltias's unintentional arrangement made it easier for Seclian. He could smoothly let the First Fleet warships and legion reserve soldiers sailing at the front carry out his orders: they were fast 3-layer oar warships. The soldiers on top all jumped into the sea; they were from the Crow Warship, 40 soldiers were retained, and the rest all jumped into the sea.  

   Of course, Seclian would also encounter friendly soldiers on the warship. They obviously resisted this order, and some even threatened to use force to occupy the ship. The captain could only patiently persuade, and at the same time, there were nearby battles. The soldiers on the ship jumped into the sea to set an example, and most of these friendly soldiers eventually obeyed, but this only delayed time...  

  --- 

   While Seclian was anxiously persuading the ships in the east to obey his orders, the East Phoenician fleet was speeding up to pursue the Theonian warships retreating towards the coast.  

   Theonia's sailors paddled hard, but the ship was full of soldiers, which seriously affected the speed of the warship. They were gradually pulled closer by the East Phoenician fleet, which had been raised to the highest speed by the warship.  

   Eastern Phoenician warships, like tigers and wolves, pounced on the fat sheep in their eyes.  

   Seeing that the Theonian warship that was lagging behind could not escape, he simply turned around and bravely rushed towards the enemy ship. However, how could the Theonian warship that had lost its speed and flexibility be able to go into battle lightly? The opponents of the Phoenician warships either had their oars broken or were hit against the hull. Theonian crew members and soldiers continued to jump into the sea screaming in surprise.  

   Of course, there are occasional exceptions. These East Phoenician sailors learned about the situation of the Theonian fleet from the mouths of their colonial compatriots, but after all, they have not experienced it personally. Several East Phoenician warships were careless when they were facing each other. Hooked by the twelve-meter-long suspension bridge of the Crow Warship, the friendly soldiers who had already put on armor and picked up weapons swarmed over.  

   Other Phoenician warships who saw this terrible scene quickly learned their lesson. When facing the Crow Warship again, they avoided the bow and attacked the stern.  

   The Raven warship was unable to move flexibly due to too many soldiers, was slow, and had no fast trireme to protect it, so it became a key target for Phoenician warships to attack.  

   Miltias's ship was rushing towards the beach. That beach happened to be the beach where the fleet infantry landed during the night raid a few days ago. It was one mile away, and the distance was getting closer, but Miltias There was no joy on his face, and he was suffering inside.  

   Originally, he had been sitting at the stern of the ship, observing the follow-up of other warships, but what he saw was: countless enemy ships rushing in at lightning speed, attacking the warships that were lagging behind. Although these lone warships were They resisted tenaciously, but were either sunk or damaged. They floated stiffly on the sea, allowing the enemy to bully them. The crew members kept screaming, and more and more crew members and soldiers fell into the sea...  

   This situation made Miltias feel like a knife: these are the warships that he had shamelessly applied to the Ministry of Military Affairs for more than ten years, carefully maintained and repaired every day, and saved up with hard work, but they were all gone in the blink of an eye! There are also these brothers who have been with him day and night and trained hard for more than ten years. He brought them to Sicily with their eagerness for meritorious service. They had never fought a big battle, but they were about to lose their lives! ...  

   He couldn't help but stood up and said loudly: "Stop the boat immediately! Leave 40 soldiers behind. The other soldiers immediately jumped off the boat and swam to the beach by themselves! Quick! Quick!"  

   At this time, the order issued by Miltias was actually the same as that of Seclian. In fact, he had this idea in his mind before, but at that time he was still lucky, and he was worried that driving the soldiers on the ship into the sea would lead to friendly wars later. The protest was not good for him. After all, he had made a big mistake... A mistake caused the Sicilian fleet to encounter difficulties, and now he regretted it.  

   The friendly soldiers on the deck did not argue like the friendly soldiers on the warship to the east, because they had already seen the bad situation on the sea behind them. Staying on the ship was not necessarily safer than being at sea, so they quickly followed suit.  

   Miltias did not command the flagship to rush directly to the enemy ships, but quickly sailed towards the approaching warships. He needed to gather the nearby warships scattered outside the battlefield as quickly as possible in order to fight against this enemy ship that came out of nowhere. The enemy fleet is coming.  

   In fact, due to the critical situation, Miltias did not need to remind him that some soldiers on the Theonian warships had already actively jumped into the sea so that the warships could participate in the battle.  

   However, the first wave of attacks by the East Phoenician fleet crashed at least 10 Theonian triremes, and had torn the already scattered rear of the Theonian fleet to pieces. The warships took advantage of the victory to pursue the scattered Theonian warships, trying to catch the rear of the Theonian fleet in one fell swoop.  

   The flagship of Miltias, with its wide hull and the red blood flag flying on the top of the mast, naturally became the main target of the East Phoenician attack. A total of five Phoenician warships sailed towards it quickly, which forced Miltias to His original plan had to be stopped.  

   Miltias made an immediate decision and issued an order to a crow warship and a fast three-layer oar warship that gathered on both sides of his ship.  

   Soon, the Crow Warship and his flagship turned around quickly and headed towards the coast, while the fast 3-layer oar warship turned around and sailed parallel to the coast, keeping distance from them.  

   


   (End of this chapter)

Chapter 900 Approaching Jera  
   Pomirka was stunned and asked: "Don't we capture the city of Selinus first?"  

   Mago's old face was slightly red, but he still said seriously: "After this period of siege, I believe you also know that Selinus is not only strong in defense, but the main force of Theonia is also in Selinus. Their morale is very good, even if our soldiers outnumber them, it will take us more time to capture this city, and time is important to me!"  

   Pomilka then remembered the promise Mago had made in the Senate. He no longer hesitated and immediately expressed his willingness to go to war.  

   Mago showed a few smiles and said generously: "You will lead 10,000 Carthaginian citizen soldiers, 15,000 citizen soldiers composed of Phoenician allies, and 25,000 Numibian soldiers. , a total of 50,000 people, which is 10,000 more than when Monte Adeno attacked Minoa! I hope you will lead the army to Minoa tomorrow, and do not make the same mistake as Monte Adeno did, as soon as possible Capture the city of Minoa!"  

   Pomilka was not excited about leading such a large army. Instead, he asked with concern: "Master Mago, according to this arrangement, there are not many soldiers left around you. What if Dionysius is in the city?" The demi-humans came out of the city to attack again..."  

   Although Pomilka did not say any more, he had already expressed his worries. In his opinion, if he followed Mago's suggestion and led his army to leave, Mago would only have less than 20,000 soldiers from Iberia left with him. The army brought by Asia, this mixed army of multiple races seems to be very effective in combat, but it is not easy to manage and lacks loyalty. There are also nearly 10,000 citizen soldiers formed by the western allies of Sicily. These Sicilians lack training and are more suitable for carrying out luggage, building camps and other chores, rather than fighting; the remaining nearly 10,000 Numibians The soldiers were soldiers from the camp that had been attacked at night before. Obviously, Theonia's attack frightened these dark-skinned Numibians. In order to prevent their panic from affecting the morale of other troops, Mago They were specially separated and have been busy training these days. They are even preparing to send them to Lilibi to replace the defenders there.  

   But Mago was not worried about this. He said confidently: "If the Theonians act like you said, that's exactly what I hope."  

   Pomilka gave up his persuasion and accepted the order. In fact, even if he didn't accept it, Mago would force him to accept it, because he had previously forcibly replaced many Carthaginian generals and replaced them with captains of the Iberian army he trusted. Not only did he let the army formed by Carthage The soldiers felt very uneasy. After the news reached Carthage, it also aroused criticism from the Senate. The Hannoists even criticized his approach, claiming that he did this just to make the entire army become Magoni. The private army of the German family was used to facilitate his dictatorship.  

   Mago asked the neutral senator Bomilcar to temporarily take over the Carthaginian army, not only to appease the soldiers, but also to reassure the senators.  

  --- 

   On the second day, Pomirka led the army out of camp and marched eastward along the coast.  

   Mago did not conceal this military action, so the large-scale mobilization of the Carthaginians in the military camp was clearly seen by Leotychides on the city top. He was a little anxious because he could guess this. He had not considered why the Carthaginian army left: he would take this opportunity to lead the entire army out of the city to attack the Carthaginian army still in the camp. However, the previous night attack had already sounded the alarm for the Carthaginians. Since he still dares to do this, he is obviously on guard.  

   Leotychides holds the only main force of the Kingdom of Theonia on Sicily. When the enemy is outnumbered, he can only take actions with a high chance of winning, so he is now anxiously looking forward to it. Arrival of Catanai's fleet.  

  --- 

   Hasdrubal allowed the soldiers to plunder and massacre the entire city of Agrigento. On the one hand, it was to commemorate his father Himilko (himilko also once led the army to occupy the city of Agrigento) and let his soldiers After experiencing arduous marches and hard battles in mountainous areas, the soldiers can be released and gain something; on the other hand, it is also to obtain enough food.  

   His purpose was achieved. The territory of Agrigento is either mountainous or hilly. Although it is not famous for agriculture, it is a famous livestock city in Sicily. Therefore, Hasdrubal obtained a large number of livestock, enough to maintain a population of 20,000 people. Food for the army for half a month.  

   So after a day's rest, while Pomirka was marching towards Minoa, Hasdrubal left 1,000 soldiers to garrison the city of Agrigento and led 16,000 soldiers to march eastward along the coast. , the target is Jera.  

   The army had to pass through the city of Econoume on its way forward. Why didn't Leotychides transport reinforcements to this city before, and why didn't Hasdrubal target this city? Because this is a small Greek city, its size is only slightly larger than Germe. The low city walls can only be used to block wild beasts, but cannot block the enemy's attack at all, so Leotychides does not have hope for it, haha Sdruba didn't see it as a hindrance, either. (Note: Historically, it was a hundred years later that the tyrants of Agrigento built a new city on Cape Econome. During the First Punic War a few decades later, on the promontory of this city The largest naval battle in ancient Western history took place nearby. Carthage and Rome invested a total of 680 warships, carrying about 290,000 sailors and soldiers, and Rome ultimately won.)  
   Sure enough, when Hasdrubal arrived with his army, the residents of Econom had already fled, leaving only an empty city. The Carthaginian army entered successfully.  

   After resting for a night, we continued marching eastward on the second day and entered the Jela territory at noon.  

   The city of Gela has a long history. It was only four or five years later than the founding of Syracuse. It was founded by colonists from Rhodes Island and Crete. The city was named after the Gela River in the territory.  

   Because the Jela River washed away a large amount of soil from the mountains, it formed a fertile river plain in the Jela territory. After decades of successful transformation of the river swamps by the Jela people, Jela became prosperous, and this At that time, the city of Agrigento had just been established, and the city of Syracuse was still limited to the island of Ortygia. Therefore, Hippocrates, the well-equipped tyrant of Gera a hundred years ago, and his successor Dilon launched an attack eastward. After the war of conquest, eventually all the Greek colonial cities in eastern Sicily, including Messina and Camanlina, surrendered to Gela. Dillon took a fancy to Syracuse's geographical location and moved there, leaving his Brother Hieron took over Gela and moved half of the population of Gela, where he was born, to Syracuse, thus creating the beginning of Syracuse's prosperity. After Dillon's death, Hieron moved to Syracuse... After that, the tyrants of Gela abandoned their original city one after another and made Syracuse their center of rule. Gela was also the strongest in Sicily. The large Greek city-states began to decline. But by this point, Gera had also established a fairly close relationship with Syracuse.  

   The first conflict between Gela and Syracuse occurred more than 20 years ago. Carthage commander Himilco led his army on the way to attack Syracuse. He first occupied Agrigento and then surrounded it. Jera. Dionysius promised to send reinforcements, but in the end the reinforcements never arrived and Gela was captured. The contradiction deepened after the Gera people returned to their homeland. Syracuse had become the overlord of the Greek city-states in Sicily. Dionysius exploited and oppressed the people of the allies very hard, which of course included Gera. The people of La La were very dissatisfied with him, but were afraid of his powerful force and could only obey.  

   Until Theonia defeated Syracuse, although the Gera people were grateful to the Theonia, they were also wary of outsiders entering Sicily. Theonia had been friendly with the city-states around Sicily for 10 years. , which made the Jela people finally let down their guard. In this war between Theonia and Carthage, Jela also actively provided material assistance and sent troops to participate in the war.  

   Now, the Carthaginian army is approaching the city. This not only makes the Gera people nervous, but also shocks Syracuse and Catanai. After all, compared with the previous series of battles in the west, Gera is very far away from them. The closer it is, the more likely it is to attract people's attention.  

  --- 

   "Commander, Chalcides is here." Muklu reported to Leotychides.  

   "Ask him to come in."  

   A middle-aged team officer wearing a purple crowned helmet strode into the hall of the city lord's mansion.  

   His name was Chalcides, and he was from Catanai. After Dionysius conquered Catanai, he became a refugee and fled to a settlement in the mountains for a period of time. Later, he quietly returned to the port of Catanai and made a living by selling his labor. He was not afraid of rape and helped He is weak and fair in dealing with things, so he has a high prestige among the refugees and free people in Catanai Port. During the South-Italian War, Antrapolis lurked in the port of Catanai and received great help from him. In the subsequent riots in Catanai, the free people he led were also one of the main forces. After Catanay's successful recovery, he also led his troops to assist the First Legion in pursuing Mathias' defeated army.  

   However, after the war ended and Catanai was merged into the Kingdom of Theonia, the hero in the hearts of the Catanai people refused to become a kingdom official or a member of the city council. Instead, he volunteered to be a tribune, and Every year, he is elected by the Catanai people for his outstanding performance to participate in the Kingdom's Tribune Conference. At the same time, he was also the captain of the first battalion of the Eighth Legion, and was deeply relied on by Leotychides.  

   "Your Majesty Commander, Chalcedis is here to report!" Chalcedis gave a powerful military salute.  

   (End of this chapter)

Chapter 901 The Seventh Legion comes for reinforcements  
   Leotychides showed a rare smile at this moment and asked: "How is the situation in the military camp today?"  

   Since capturing Selinus, Leotychides has temporarily assumed the responsibility of managing the entire city (although most of the people in Selinus have been escorted to Catanai), and naturally there are not many He devoted his time and energy to the army, so he usually asked Chalcedis to manage the military camp for him. So far, no major mistakes have occurred.  

   "Everything is going well. The defeat of the navy did not affect the morale of the brothers. On the contrary, they hope that your Lord will allow them to raid the enemy camp again and achieve several more military exploits." Chalcedis replied.  

   Leotychides shook his head lightly: "The Carthaginians have already been fooled once. The same strategy will hardly work again, but I am prepared to conduct a major military operation..."  

   At this point, he looked at Chalcedis.  

   Chalcides stood with a steady expression and did not show any eagerness.  

   Leotychides praised in his heart, with the same indifferent expression on his face: "Now the Carthaginians have divided their army into four parts, one part is besieging Selinus, one part is attacking Minoa, and the other part is attacking Enna , and some are attacking Jela, the situation is very serious. If you were me, what would you do at this time? "  

   For senior team officers like Chalcedis, the information obtained by spies and clippers is generally open to them, so Chalcedis has a better understanding of the current battlefield situation and has his own thoughts, so he thought Thinking, he said: "The Carthaginian army is far more numerous than us, but since they are spreading their attacks, we can use the advantages of the sea to defeat them one by one."  

   "Destroy each one...well..." Leotychides asked again calmly: "Where do you think we should start?"  

   "Gela." Chalcedis said without hesitation: "The Carthaginian army there is said to be not that large in strength, and it is alone and deep in the sea. It is also close to the coast. It is the best target for attack!"  

   Leotychides nodded: "You and I want to go together. I am going to lead the Eighth Legion and the 4th Cavalry Legion to Gela by boat to defeat this Carthaginian army as soon as possible. After I leave , you will lead 5,000 legion reserve soldiers to stay here."  

   Chalcides did not respond immediately, but showed hesitation, which surprised Leotyzides who knew him well.  

   After a moment, Chalcedis resolutely said: "Commander, 5,000 soldiers are too many, 3,000 are enough. In this way, sir, you will have more soldiers to defeat the Carthaginian army. I am confident that we can hold on." Until you lead your team to victory and return!"  

   Leotychides looked slightly stunned. He sat on a wooden chair and looked directly at Chalsidis for a while. Then he stood up, walked to him, stretched out his hand and patted his shoulder: "I After leading the army to leave Selinus for the first time, not only to defeat the Carthaginian army in Gela, I am afraid that we will not come back for a long time, and Selinus is very important to us, so we must try our best. Guard it, that's why I have left so many soldiers for you, and you don't have to worry about the small number of troops I lead. When we get to the east, I will have plenty of soldiers to use."  

   After hearing this, Chalcedis immediately said solemnly: "Commander, please rest assured, as long as I am here, the city of Selinus is here, and I will definitely defend Selinus to the death!"  

   Leotychides twitched his face, and his tone was rare and gentle: "If you really can't hold on, you don't need to hold on. There is a navy fleet at the port to bring the soldiers home safely. This war will be very long. , we will have the opportunity to take Selinus back in the future..."  

  --- 

   Cartanae's fleet arrived at the port of Selinus. Leotyzides led his army to prepare to board the ship, and happened to encounter a messenger sent by Minoa to ask for help.  

   It turned out that after Bomilcar led the Carthaginian army to the territory of Minoa and set up camp, he began to attack the city of Minoa. Unlike Monte Adeno, Pomircar personally went to the front line to supervise the siege. Coupled with the iron-blooded command from the generals of the Iberian army, the soldiers did not dare to slack off and attacked fiercely, which brought great harm to the Minoan defenders. pressure.  

   At this time, Leotychides had no good solution after receiving the news. He could only comfort the Minoans and insist on holding on for a while, and he would lead his army to rescue them as soon as possible.  

   Under the escort of the Sicilian fleet, the fleet of Leotychides' army successfully entered the port of Gela.  

  --- 

   At the same time, the commander of the Seventh Army, Brelu, who was at Camp Locri, received an order from the Ministry of Military Affairs: The Seventh Army will go to Catanay today. Urgent!  
   "It's finally our turn!" Brelu's strong body jumped up from the seat and shouted excitedly to the adjutant: "Send someone quickly to inform Chief Lokli and ask them to prepare for the expedition. Also Have...notified all the brigades of this news and asked them to recall the soldiers who were out immediately!"  

   "Yes, legion commander!"  

   Not long after, there were continuous cheers in the military camp.  

   Breleu smiled after hearing this.  

   Brelu was once the leader of Bruti in the city of Bisignia. Later Bisignia was merged into Theonia. He became a senator, but he did not engage in government affairs like Baguilipi, but chose to join Theonia. Nia Legion. During the South Italian War, he was the first captain of the Fourth Legion. As a result, he was captured by Dionysius along with the legion commander Dracos. Dracos was killed, but he was imprisoned because of his status as the former leader of Bruti. and was eventually rescued. As the only senior officer of the Theonian Legion who was captured by the Syracuseans in the South Italian War and survived, he regarded this as the greatest shame and always fought bravely in the subsequent wars. Due to his merits, he was promoted to commander of the Seventh Legion.  

   In this war, other legions have participated in the war, but the Seventh Legion has remained idle so far. Brelu has written to the Ministry of Military Affairs many times complaining about injustice. Not long ago, the Ministry of Military Affairs sent a message saying that the Carthaginian army had landed in Sicily again, reminding him to prepare in advance.  

   Brelu began to issue summoning orders for the Seventh Army to the surrounding towns. Now the Seventh Army in the military camp is fully staffed. The soldiers have high morale and are waiting to go into battle to kill the enemy and make meritorious deeds.  

   But soon, the reply from the Locri City Hall poured cold water on Breluxian, because there were not enough passenger ships to transport troops in the Locri port for the time being, and it would take another day or two to make preparations.  

   Brelu was frustrated.  

   At this time, the adjutant reminded: "There is no ship in Locke, but there is also Lijim!"  

   Brelu's eyes lit up: In the past, the soldiers of the Seventh Legion came from Locri, Hibernian and Colonia, but after Lijim and his son Bontaurina were completely integrated into the kingdom last year, these two cities were also The Ministry of Military Affairs included the Seventh Army's troop source area, but because the relationship had not been straightened out and the war broke out, the Seventh Army had not yet issued a notice asking the military training officers of Lijim and Taurina to arrange for their citizens to go to Lokli. The military camp participated in rotation training. Although there are currently no Lijim citizens in the Seventh Army, Lijim, as a port city guarding the Strait of Messina, has many ships, which can completely help transport troops.  

   Brelu immediately said: "Send a messenger to Lijim as soon as possible and ask for their support!"  

   The next day, Lijim responded to the Seventh Legion's request, and nearly two hundred passenger ships sailed into the port of Locri at dusk.  

   Early on the morning of the third day, Brelu led the 7th Army of more than 8,000 people to leave the military camp and enter the city of Locri. The people of Locri gathered on both sides of the street to say goodbye to their relatives. Different from the people in other cities in the kingdom who saw off the army, they rarely shouted, were not overly excited, and did not rush into the streets to hinder the march. Instead, they stood by the streets in an orderly manner and kept waving. .  

   Although after joining the Kingdom of Theonia, Locri no longer implemented the cruel laws enacted by Zaleukus, and no more disabled people appeared in more than 10 years, the citizens of this city have integrated restraint and obedience. In his own blood, this also allowed Locri, who was originally an enemy of Theonia, to hardly cause any trouble to King Davos and the Senate after merging into the kingdom. Of course, the Locri citizens who believe in Persephone and pay attention to the rule of law are also an important reason why they easily identify with the Kingdom of Theonia.  

   Before entering the port, the army also passed by Lockley's shipbuilding workshop: seven or eight large dry docks were lined up on the beach, and many shipwrights were building triremes inside; Stacks of thick tree trunks were cut down, and from time to time there were teams of horse-drawn carriages carrying trees into the workshop; in many temporary wooden sheds, carpenters were constantly processing rough tree trunks into pieces. Straight and smooth ship plates... People in the entire workshop are focused on the work at hand, and few people are distracted to watch the Seventh Legion passing by here.  

   This lively and orderly shipbuilding scene is not only found in Locri, but also in other seaside towns with shipbuilding capabilities, such as: Thurii, Crotone, Trina, Siliting, Lijim, Tower Lantum, Catanai, Naxos... the entire Theonian Kingdom is making every effort to build more warships as soon as possible in order to continue to gain maritime superiority in the war with Carthage.  

   In the morning, the fleet carrying the soldiers of the Seventh Legion left the port of Locri and sailed to Catanai on the eastern coast of Sicily.  

  --- 

   Although Midorades was very excited after receiving the order from King Davos, he did not immediately lead the fleet to invade Corsica because he targeted Aleni as his first target. Compared with the small village-like strongholds of the Phoenicians scattered across Corsica, Alenia, as the only Phoenician town in Corsica, has small but fertile agricultural land and rich mining industries. And a larger port, no doubt let Midorades hang down three feet.  

   


   (End of this chapter)

Chapter 902: Capture of Alesia  
   But he also knew that Alenia was not easy to attack. According to the information he learned from the intelligence department, the city had more than 3,000 citizen soldiers and a 6-7 meter high wall. In the event of a battle, the city would be closed. Defend, for the Third Fleet with only 6,000 fleet infantry, it will cost a lot to attack.  

   Furthermore, Midorades was good at naval warfare and had no experience in land warfare.  

   Medorades knew his capabilities, so he did not act blindly, but summoned his men to discuss.  

   Maeontides, the commander of the fleet infantry, put forward his own suggestion: lure the citizen soldiers of Alenia out of the city and eliminate them, thus weakening their ability to defend the city, making it easier to attack the city again. (There are 4 fleet infantry officers in the Theonian army sequence. They are affiliated to the four major fleets respectively. They are the No. 2 person in the fleet. They need to obey the command of the fleet commander and own and manage and train all the fleets in peacetime. Infantry, the right to command the troops to land on the coast to conduct surprise operations and invade enemy territory during war. The number of infantry in the fleet under his command is not fixed, depending on the number of crow warships in his fleet.), and the lure The solution was to dress up as an Etruscan pirate and raid the silver mines of Alenia.  

   For hundreds of years, the two most famous pirate groups on the Italian peninsula were the Illyrians on the Adriatic on the east coast and the Etruscans on the west coast. Unlike the Illyrians who were pirates mainly for survival, the Etruscan pirates were originally formed privately by the Etruscan city-states in order to combat the ongoing colonization of the Italian peninsula and began to threaten the Etruscans. The Greeks were hegemonic in central and northern Italy. As the wave of Greek colonization to the western Mediterranean weakened and the final spheres of influence of both sides were determined, Etruscan pirates decreased significantly.  

   But 30 years ago, the number of Etruscan pirates increased again. The reason was not due to official organization, but because the Celts in northern Italy began to invade southward and seize the Etruscan lands. Especially more than ten years ago, the Celtic army swept through the entire Etruscan territory and even captured Rome. Many Etruscans fled to the sea and became pirates. Even after the Gauls retreated, there were still some Some Etruscans, having tasted the sweetness of getting something for nothing, wanted to continue raiding the west coast of Italy.  

   However, during this period, due to the establishment of the third fleet of Theonia, which strengthened its patrols on the coast of the Kingdom of Theonia and its allies, the frequently attacked Etruscan pirates were greatly reduced again and could only huddle on the west coast of Italy. In the north, they dare not go south. Although Carthage once formed an alliance with Etruria and still maintains a tacit understanding of neighborly relations and non-aggression, Alenia has been invaded by Etruscan pirates in the past.  

   After Myontides' suggestion was adopted, Midorades began to make careful preparations. He even went to the newly occupied Etruscan city of Keslera to learn more about the Etruscan pirates. In order to cope with the situation, several Etruscan cargo ships and the armor and weapons of their soldiers were also borrowed.  

   Two days later, dozens of warships of the 3rd Fleet, loaded with fleet soldiers, quietly docked at nightfall on the beach between Alenia and the Etruscan town of Mariana in the north. 4,000 fleet soldiers The infantry landed ashore and sneaked into the mountains.  

   On the second day, several Etruscan ships suddenly broke into the offshore of Alenia and docked on the northern beach of Alenia. More than 200 "Etruscan pirates" landed ashore and rushed towards A famous silver mine in the mountains of northwest Alenia.  

   Ever since the Theonian army landed in the Latium area, the Alenians have been on tenterhooks, but a month or two later, the Theonian army did not land on Corsica, and even in the offshore area With no trace of the Theonian warships in sight, the Alenians were temporarily relieved. They thought that the Theonian army was still trapped in the war with Rome and could not get out. Unexpectedly, at this time, the hateful Itte Lurian pirates appeared, and they wanted to plunder a large silver mine in Alenia, which was an important source of revenue for the Alenia treasury.  

   After detailed exploration by the clipper, no other abnormalities were found offshore. Considering the difficulty of the Etruscan pirates, for the sake of safety, the Carthaginian judges in Alenia decided to deal with them as soon as possible to avoid Other accidents occurred, so he urged the city hall to quickly summon 800 Alenian citizen soldiers. He led this army out of the city and quickly rushed to the location of the silver mines.  

   When they launched an attack on the Etruscan pirates who were plundering the silver mines, 4,000 fleet infantry suddenly appeared behind them and surrounded them.  

   The Alenian army was quickly defeated, the Carthaginian judges died in the battle, and the soldiers were either killed or captured.  

   The fleet infantry first separated them into separate groups for interrogation, and then reunited and escorted them toward the beach. On the way, the Alesian prisoners at the front of the team suddenly rioted and knocked down the soldiers escorting them. Then the prisoners, whose faces were covered with blood and filth, returned to save their other companions.  

   Suddenly, the entire escort team fell into chaos. Many Alesians seized the opportunity to escape. By the time the fleet infantry calmed down the commotion, more than 200 prisoners had already fled towards the city of Alenia.  

   So, the fleet soldiers began to chase.  

   The prisoners ran away regardless of fatigue and fled to the city, shouting hysterically: "Open the door quickly!! The Theonians are coming! Open the door quickly!!..."  

   For hundreds of years, the Alenians have lived a peaceful and peaceful life under the protection of Carthage, except for occasionally fighting pirates. Suddenly they heard the news that "the Theonians were coming to kill", and the defenders at the top of the city They were all at a loss when they saw the disheveled and embarrassed compatriots under the city. The people shouting were all familiar people. The dust and smoke were billowing in the distance, and it was obvious that the enemy was approaching quickly.  

   So they opened the city gate without hesitation and urged the deserters to come in quickly.  

   As soon as the prisoners ran into the city, dozens of fleet infantry hidden among them pulled out the short swords tied to their backs and hidden by loose linings, and stabbed the prisoners beside them.  

   The city gate suddenly fell into chaos, causing a blockage and unable to be closed immediately.  

   The large fleet infantry force arrived soon after and took advantage of the situation to rush into the city...  

   After a period of fighting within the city, Alenia was captured.  

  --- 

   At dusk, the deep and deep sound of bugles rang outside the city of Satnicum, and the Theonian soldiers who were attacking the city retreated like a tide.  

   In the large tent in the military camp, Tormid was reporting to Davos: "Your Majesty, we have launched continuous attacks on Satnicum in the past few days. The Romans' defense was quite tenacious, which prevented our attack. If any progress has been made, the casualties of the soldiers have been close to 3,000, and the soldiers are tired and morale is low after days of hard fighting..."  

   "Tormid, you are wrong. The morale of the brothers is still very high. They are eager to attack the city and avenge their dead comrades! Moreover, we have casualties, and the casualties of the Romans are not small. They are more numerous than us. Much less, and if we attack for a few more days, they won't be able to withstand it!" Amyntas retorted loudly.  

   Tormid did not argue, but just looked at Davos.  

   Davos looked solemn and tapped his fingers on the table.  

   After a moment, he said: "The Romans are different from other enemies. They are well-disciplined and tenacious in fighting spirit, no less than our legionnaires. Moreover, their commander Camillus is very capable. They have been very successful in defense these days." This sudden attack caused us a lot of trouble.  

   For an army with tenacious fighting spirit, the more violent our attack, the more violent the resistance will be. And Tormid is right. Since our soldiers landed in Latium, how many major battles have been carried out in a few months, such as siege battles, raids, pursuit battles... before they can be seen in just a few short days. To defeat Rome and conquer such a large territory within a few months, it's time to slow down! The soldiers are all made of flesh, not made of iron. Even if they are iron, they will bend after constant impact... Therefore, I decided to stop the siege of Satnikum starting from tomorrow.  

   I think... the last time a rugby match was held in the city of Rome, it was very popular among the soldiers. Can we continue to hold rugby and football matches in the camp? We can expand the scope of the game and start with competitions between the brigades of each legion. , the winning team will participate in the competition between the various legions. Whether it is the final winning team within the legion or the championship team between legions, they will receive generous rewards, allowing the soldiers to relax and be happy. "  

   When talking about the favorite sport of legionnaires, several legion commanders all smiled and even claimed that it was.  

   According to the military concept of the Romans, war is the most important event related to the life and death of a city-state. Citizens gather to go out to fight, kill the enemy and return, always going all out. There has never been any competition and fun in the camp, but since then After participating in the competition last time, Sextus has been fascinated by this new game. At this moment, his face was full of joy, and he specifically asked: "Your Majesty, will you take us to compete this time?!" (According to Sextus Due to Stus' military position, he could not have appeared at Davos's military meeting, but now the Roman reserves have become a force that cannot be ignored in the Theonian army, whether for military considerations or Due to political considerations, every time Davos held a military meeting, Tormid had to notify him)  

   "This is absolutely not possible!" Matonis objected loudly, with an extremely firm attitude: "Your Majesty, you cannot participate, otherwise other legions will not be able to compete seriously!"  

   "Don't worry, I'm just a spectator this time." Davos looked at the anxious and pale-faced Matonis with a smile, and then looked at the somewhat disappointed Sextus: "However, the reserve soldiers are really not very good at playing. Rugby, let alone football, it's not fair for your legion to compete against them..."  

   (End of this chapter)

Chapter 909 Adding insult to injury  
   "Yes!" Muklu commanded the messengers to rush everywhere, shouting loudly to the retreating legionnaires.  

   And Leotychides has already led the guards towards the north gate. He needs to return to the city first and quickly and best arrange with the Gera people to respond to the broken troops and defend the enemy from taking advantage of the chaos to attack the city.  

   The flag bearer in the guard held the legion's flag high and fluttered in the wind. It pointed the direction for the retreating Eighth Legion soldiers.  

   The enemy's defeat seemed to inject vitality into Hasdroba's tired body. He followed the Lusitanian warriors to hunt down the fleeing enemies.  

   At this time, the Lusitanians' ability to run was fully utilized, and the heavy armor of the Greek heavy infantry allowed them to be easily overtaken by the enemy.  

   Hasdrubal led the soldiers to kill all the way, and in the end everyone turned into a bloody man.  

   When they pursued them to the bottom of the city and tried to take the opportunity to attack the city, javelins and arrows poured down from the top of the city, causing many casualties to them who were unprepared.  

   Hasdrubal saw many black-helmeted and black-armored defenders on the top of the city. He did not dare to continue attacking the broken troops crowded under the city. Instead, he turned around and chased the broken troops in other directions...  

   It was not until dusk that the Carthaginian army withdrew its troops and returned to camp.  

  --- 

   In this battle, the 4th Theonian Cavalry Corps lost half of its cavalry, and the 8th Corps suffered about 1,300 casualties, of which more than half of the light armor and light infantry brigade were lost. The Jela Army suffered more than 2,000 casualties. The casualties were the highest. Of the 3,000 soldiers who originally went to battle, only more than 300 fled back. The entire coalition suffered nearly 7,000 casualties. The Carthaginian army suffered more than 2,000 casualties, among which the Balearic slingers suffered the most casualties, more than half.  

   Due to the retreat of the Theonia coalition, most of the injured coalition soldiers failed to escape.  

   The battle of Gela severely damaged the citizen soldiers of Gela and Camanlina, making the troops that Leotyzides could command even more stretched. More importantly, "the Carthaginians defeated Dio, who had been winning consecutive battles before. The news of the "Nian Army" was like a stone thrown into Sicily's seemingly calm political situation, causing ripples in some city-states.  

   After the Battle of Gela, despite repeated calls for help from the Minoans, Leotychides continued to stay at Gela, resting his troops while resisting the Carthaginian siege. As the number of troops under his command became smaller and smaller, he was even more unwilling to dismantle them and station them in various city-states, otherwise they would only be eaten one by one by the Carthaginian army. Moreover, compared to Minoa, he believed that Gera strategic location is even more important.  

   Of course, he could not just sit back and ignore Minoa, so he sent a messenger, together with the Minoian messenger, to Pacinus to ask for help.  

  --- 

   On the fourth day after the Battle of Gela, the Sicilian Governor Sipulos in Catanai received an urgent report from Serofennis, the head of the kingdom's intelligence department in Sicily: a military mobilization was underway in the city of Syracuse, and its motive was unknown. .  

   For the sake of caution, Sipulus immediately sent a messenger to notify the Seventh Legion, which had arrived at Catanai and was ordered to go to Hena, so that it could rush back quickly and garrison the new military camp near Leotini to prevent accidents.  

   But the accident still happened. Pacinus promised to rescue Minoa and sent 3,000 reinforcements. Shortly after leaving the port by ship, he suddenly encountered Syracuse's fleet.  

   In recent years, the eastern waters of Sicily have been dominated by the Theonian Second Fleet. The Syracuse Navy, which once dominated Sicily, has long lost its glory and has shrunk into a fleet of only 30 three-tier warships and a total of 50 warships. The small fleet, which usually only patrols the sea near its own city-state, suddenly appeared on the sea near Pachinus and launched an attack on the troop transport fleet.  

   Since the Theonian Sicilian fleet has been stationed in Selinus during this period, it was alerting the western seas and concerned about the war in Selinus, and did not send any warships to escort it. Of course, the Pacinos did not make any demands to Catanai. After all, it is far away from the battlefield, the nearby sea has always been safe, has close relations with Theonia, and is in harmony with its neighbor Syracuse. They believe that from now on It should be safe to sail from your own city-state to Minoa. Therefore, the Pacinus people only sent their city-state's only five three-layer oar warships to escort them, as a symbolic show.  

   As a result, after being suddenly attacked by the Syracuse fleet, the Pacinus warships resisted tenaciously, but were outnumbered. Except for four troop transports, which escaped back to the port, all the others were sunk.  

   At the same time, Syracuse sent an army of 12,000 men. Instead of marching north to attack Taunis, which was very close to it, Syracuse turned around and headed south, quickly rushing to Camanlina to attack the outside world. The claim was "to help the Camanlinans to resist the invasion of the Carthaginians."  

   After the people of Camanlina rejected the request of the Syracuse army to enter the city, the Syracuse army immediately changed their attitude and surrounded the city of Camanlina. While preparing to attack the city, they sent envoys into the city to threaten Camanlina. Naren: Syracuse has already formed an alliance with Carthage. It can either re-affiliate to Syracuse so that it can be protected when the Carthage army arrives; or choose to refuse and Syracuse will attack the city and after the city is defeated , the people in the city will be handed over to the Carthaginians.  

   Since Camanlina has sent most of its citizen soldiers to assist Gela, there are only more than 500 Camanlina citizen soldiers who can fight in the city at this time. Time to consider.  

   The Syracuse envoy was so arrogant that he only gave him one day.  

   After the envoy returned, the Syracuse army not only immediately blocked the road from Camanlina to Gela, but also the Syracuse warships blocked its port.  

   At this time, the Carthaginian army that had won the battle had moved its camp eastward and intensified the siege of the city of Gela, so Leotychides was busy dealing with the Carthaginian siege and attacking Carman. Nothing was known about what happened to Lina.  

   Half a day later, a Theonian merchant ship ventured into the port and brought news: the Syracuse fleet attacked the troop transport fleet of Pacinus and blocked the ports of Pacinus and Camanlina.  

   When Leotychides found out, he was shocked: Syracuse finally joined the war!  
   The addition of Syracuse will undoubtedly worsen Theonia's predicament in Sicily, especially on the south coast. The Theonia coalition is not only more disadvantaged in terms of numbers, but also falls into a dangerous situation of being attacked from both sides in terms of strategic situation. .  

   Even if Leotychides wanted to reinforce Camanlina, he was unable to do anything for a while. The Carthaginian army was threatening him by land, and the Syracuse fleet was blocking his way by sea. Without fleet escort, I am afraid that the fleet will not even be able to enter the port of Camanlina, so it will feed the fish and shrimps.  

   Leoticides sent the Theonian clipper docked in the port of Gela, and immediately rushed to notify Seclian in Selinus.  

   One day later, the confused Camanlina people saw the dark Syracuse soldiers carrying ladders and pushing tall siege equipment at the city wall, approaching the city wall. They were frightened and feared that they would be attacked by Agora. The people of Camanlina finally chose to surrender after the tragic experience of Rizhento.  

   More than 10 years later, due to the strength of the Kingdom of Theonia and the long-term friendly exchanges with the Camanlina people, there are almost no pro-Syracuse citizens in the city of Camanlina, making Syracuse who captured the city The people of Syracuse were unable to establish a government close to them for the time being. In order to prevent rebellion, they demanded that the Camanlinans hand over many protons and at the same time allow 3,000 Syracuse soldiers to garrison the city, euphemistically calling it "Once in Carthage" The arrival of the Ki army can effectively prevent its destruction of Kamanlina.  

   In addition, the Syracusans also requested that the remaining 500 Camanlina soldiers be transferred to join the Syracuse army for coordinated operations.  

   The people of Kamanlina, now a man for the sword and me for the fish, finally agreed to these conditions.  

   After the Syracuse army gained the attachment of Camanlina, they did not lead their army westward to join the Carthaginian army that was besieging Gela. Instead, they entered the city of Camanlina, leaving 3,000 soldiers to garrison. The rest of the soldiers arrived by boat and landed near the coast of Pacinus. They immediately surrounded the city of Pacinus and sent envoys into the city, asking it to surrender to Syracuse.  

   The Syracuse envoy threatened: If Pachinus refuses this request, Syracuse will not only immediately execute the more than 2,000 citizens of Pachinus (the Syracuse fleet sank the Pacchinus troop transport After the team, they did not leave, but rescued the citizens of Pachinus who fell into the water and captured them), and then led the army to attack the city of Pachinus. After the city was broken, all the people in the city would be sold. To the Carthaginians, as slaves.  

   The threat of Syracuse frightened the people of Pachinus. Their city was surrounded by the Syracuse army, and the port was blocked by Syracuse warships. The people looked at the thousands of people below the city with tearful eyes. With their relatives kneeling and tied to the ground, looking tired and haggard, the panic-stricken Pacinos held an emergency citizens' meeting and quickly reached a unanimous opinion. This had been going on before the Theonians entered Sicily. Pachinus, a city-state affiliated with Syracuse, was once again attached to Syracuse.  

   Within a few days, Syracuse successively included Pacinus and Camanlina into its alliance. In a blink of an eye, the entire southeastern corner of Sicily once again became the sphere of influence of Syracuse. It has always been a dream Citizens rejoiced as they relived the glory of Syracuse.  

   Theagenes, the chief general of Syracuse, who proposed this plan and vigorously implemented it despite the opposition of his colleagues, was highly praised by the people, and his reputation greatly increased for a while.  

   But at the same time, some people expressed dissatisfaction with Theagenis' approach. For example, the general Sictas publicly questioned: "Just to obtain two small city-states, Syracuse took great risks to anger Powerful Theonia, this is very dangerous! Theagenis, don't forget that the Carthaginians are far away in Africa, and our Syracuse is right next to Theonia!"  

   


   (End of this chapter)